Viewers, I lay my hand upon you to release you from that pain of the past.
I lay my hand upon you. Be released, in the name of Jesus!
Pain of the past - be released, in the name of Jesus!
Receive that nature of God, in the name of Jesus!
In Jesus Christ's name!
Amen!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Viewers, wherever you are, you just need to be under the influence of this telecast,
influence of our words.
With God, all things are possible.
Remember, your heart is a prayer room, a contact for God.
Make sure you are free.
Put your past behind you.
Don't hold a grudge against a brother.
If you do so, you have already grieved the Holy Spirit.
Viewers, are you there?
Wait for a Word from the Lord.
Here is the message for you. Here are God's promises - healing, blessing, salvation.
I command healing on you, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
God is not a man that lies.
Here are God's promises for you - healing, blessing, salvation.
I command healing on you, in the name of Jesus!
Wherever you have those sicknesses and diseases,
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Your body is not a temple of sickness; it is a temple of the Holy Ghost.
Holy Ghost!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Your body is a temple of the Holy Ghost.
In the name of Jesus Christ!
Listen once again - here are God's promises for you - healing, blessing, salvation.
Begin to walk in the light of your healing, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
I lay my hand upon you.
Affliction, in the name of Jesus, leave!
Leave, in the name of Jesus Christ!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Have you been touched by Jesus Christ by praying along with Prophet T.B. Joshua on Emmanuel TV?
Don't forget to send us your photos or video footage of what happened to you during the prayer -
for the glory of God!
Post your pictures or videos on Facebook, Twitter or Instagram using the hashtags -
#PrayWithTBJoshua, #DistanceIsNotABarrier or #TouchTheScreen.
Alternatively, you can upload them to our testimony website - i.emmanuel.tv -
or send them via email to info@emmanuel.tv with the subject: 'TESTIMONY'.
Remember, distance is NOT a barrier to the Holy Spirit!